♪ I'M GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA HAVE MYSELF
A TIME ♪
♪ FRIENDLY FACES
EVERYWHERE ♪
♪ HUMBLE FOLKS
WITHOUT TEMPTATION ♪
♪ GOING DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA LEAVE
MY WOE'S BEHIND ♪
♪ AMPLE PARKING
DAY OR NIGHT ♪
♪ PEOPLE SPOUTING
"HOWDY NEIGHBOR" ♪
♪ HEADED ON
UP TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ GONNA SEE IF
I CAN'T UNWIND ♪
( mumbling )
♪ SO COME ON DOWN
TO SOUTH PARK ♪
♪ AND MEET SOME
FRIENDS OF MINE ♪
HEY, WHERE'S
THE SCHOOL BUS?
WE'RE GONNA BE LATE
FOR FOOTBALL PRACTICE.
HIYA SPARKY.
WHO'S THAT?
THAT'S MY NEW
DOG SPARKY.
HE FOLLOWED ME
TO THE BUS STOP.
WOW, COOL!
GOOD BOY SPARKY,
WHO'S MY BEST BUDDY?
WHO'S MY BUDDY...
WHO'S MY BUDDY?
YOU'RE MAKING ME
SICK, DUDE!
HE'S PART DOBERMAN
AND PART WOLF.
HE'S THE TOUGHEST DOG
ON THE MOUNTAIN.
NO WAY, EVERYBODY
KNOWS THAT SYLVESTER
IS THE TOUGHEST DOG
IN SOUTH PARK.
GRRR!
HE'S NOT MEANER
THAN SPARKY!
OH YEAH,
LET'S SEE.
HEY SYLVESTER!
SPARKY WILL
KICK HIS ASS!
I'LL PUT A DOLLAR
ON SYLVESTER.
YOU'RE ON,
DUDE!
THAT'S IT SPARKY,
KICK HIS ASS!
HMM, HE'S DOING
SOMETHING TO HIS ASS.
HE'S NOT KICKING
HIS ASS,
BUT HE'S DEFINITELY DOING
SOMETHING TO HIS ASS.
SPARKY, BAD DOG!
( mumbling )
WHAT?!
DUDE, I THINK
YOUR DOG IS GAY.
WHAT DO YOU MEAN?
THAT DOG IS
A GAY, HOMOSEXUAL.
HE'S JUST CONFUSED.
I THINK
THE OTHER DOG'S
THE ONE THAT'S
CONFUSED.
( mumbling )
SICK, SHUT UP DUDE!
STAN'S DOG'S
A HOMO!
STAN'S DOG'S A HOMO!
( chef )
OKAY CHILDREN,
I KNOW YOU'RE ALL EXTREMELY
EXCITED AND NERVOUS
AND ANXIOUS ABOUT
THE HOMECOMING GAME
AGAINST MIDDLE PARK.
WHO'S MIDDLE PARK?
WHAT'S
HOMECOMING?
BUT JUST REMEMBER
WHAT I TAUGHT YOU--
THAT FOOTBALL
IS LIKE MAKING LOVE
TO A REALLY
BEAUTIFUL WOMAN.
YOU CAN'T ALWAYS SCORE,
BUT WHEN YOU DO,
IT MAKES ALL THE TRY
WORTHWHILE.
NOW LET'S
START PRACTICE.
MR. CHEF, SIR?
YES PIP,
WHAT IS IT?
I STILL DON'T
HAVE A HELMET.
I KNOW PIP,
THE SCHOOL CAN'T AFFORD
HELMETS FOR EVERYBODY.
YES, BUT COULDN'T
WE ROTATE?
WHO DOESN'T HAVE
A HELMET EVERY WEEK?
DOES IT ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE ME?
YES PIP,
I'M AFRAID IT DOES.
OH.
SORRY SON.
NOW GET YOUR ASS
IN THERE!
HUT, HUT, HUT, HUT, HUT.
HUT, HUT, HUT,
HUT, HUT, HUT...
HIKE THE DAMN BALL!
AHH!
HEY, HOW'S PRACTICE
COMING THERE CHEF?
HUH... OH,
FINE, FINE.
I DON'T HAVE TO
REMIND YOU
JUST HOW IMPORTANT
THIS GAME IS
TO US SOUTH PARK ALUMNI.
ELEMENTARY SCHOOL
ALUMNI?
THAT'S AS FAR AS
MOST OF US GOT.
YOU THINK
WE HAVE A SHOT
AT BEATING THE SPREAD
AGAINST MIDDLE PARK
THIS YEAR?
I DON'T KNOW,
WHAT'S THE SPREAD?
MIDDLE PARK
BY 70 POINTS.
HMM...
I GOT IT!
I DON'T THINK
WE HAVE A CHANCE.
NONSENSE, NOT WITH
MY NEPHEW A QUARTERBACK.
RIGHT STANLEY?
HUH?
THAT-A-BOY!
GREAT PASS,
STAN!
COME ON NED,
WE GOT TO GET OUR
ASSES TO THE BOOKIE!
OKAY, THAT WAS
GOOD PRACTICE CHILDREN.
WE'LL SEE YOU HERE
AGAIN TOMORROW.
HEY STAN, ISN'T
THAT YOUR DOG?
YEAH, HE MUST HAVE FOLLOWED
ME TO FOOTBALL PRACTICE.
YOU SEE,
HE IS SMART.
UH, MY DOG REX
FOLLOWS ME
TO FOOTBALL PRACTICE
ALL THE TIME.
YEAH, BUT MY DOG FOUND
HIS OWN WAY HERE.
THAT MAKES
HIM SMARTER.
SPARKY, GET DOWN!
OH MY GOD, WHAT IS
HE DOING TO MY DOG?
THERE HE GOES AGAIN!
GET DOWN
SPARKY, DOWN!!
STAN FORGOT
TO MENTION THAT
HIS DOG IS A GAY,
HOMOSEXUAL.
MAKE HIM STOP!
( yelping )
I'M SURE GLAD
MY DOG ISN'T GAY!
MAYBE YOU SHOULD
NAME YOUR DOG SPARKETTE!
AND SO YOU SEE,
"SIMON AND SIMON" WERE
NOT BROTHERS IN REAL LIFE,
ONLY ON TELEVISION.
THANK YOU FOR THAT
PRESENTATION ERIC.
BUT THE ASSIGNMENT
WAS ON ASIAN CULTURES,
YOU GET A D-.
DAMMIT!
WHO SHOULD WE CALL
ON NEXT, MR. HAT?
HOW ABOUT STAN,
OUR LITTLE SOUTH PARK
QUARTERBACK STAR?
GOOD IDEA.
OKAY STANLEY,
YOU'RE NEXT.
I'M NOT REALLY
PREPARED EITHER.
JUST MAKE SOMETHING UP
LIKE ERIC DID.
OKAY, UMM,
ASIAN CULTURE HAS,
PLAGUED OUR FRAGILE
EARTH FOR MANY YEARS.
WE MUST END IT.
EXCELLENT, A-!
HEY!
WOW, COOL!
WAIT A MINUTE,
WHY THE HELL DOES
HE GET AN A-?!
ERIC, STANLEY JUST MIGHT
LEAD OUR TEAM TO VICTORY
AGAINST THE
MIDDLE PARK COWBOYS
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN DECADES!!
AND WE TREAT
STAR ATHLETES BETTER
BECAUSE THEY'RE
BETTER PEOPLE.
THAT'S NOT FAIR!
LIFE ISN'T FAIR KIDDO,
GET USED TO IT.
STUPID PUPPET!
DON'T FORGET YOUR
ASSIGNMENTS TONIGHT,
THEY'RE DUE TOMORROW
FOR EVERYBODY BUT STAN.
MR. GARRISON, CAN I
ASK YOU A QUESTION?
OF COURSE STANLEY,
WHAT IS IT?
WHAT'S A
HOMOSEXUAL?
OH WELL STANLEY,
I GUESS YOU CAME
TO THE RIGHT PERSON.
SIT DOWN.
STANLEY,
GAY PEOPLE...
WELL, GAY PEOPLE
ARE EVIL.
EVIL RIGHT DOWN TO
THEIR COLD BLACK HEARTS,
WHICH PUMP, NOT BLOOD
LIKE YOURS AND MINE,
BUT RATHER
A THICK VOMITUS OIL
THAT OOZES THROUGH
THEIR ROTTEN VEINS,
AND CLOTS IN THEIR
PEA-SIZED BRAINS,
WHICH BECOMES THE CAUSE
OF THEIR NAZI-ESQUE PATTERNS
OF VIOLENT BEHAVIOR.
DO YOU UNDERSTAND?
I GUESS.
GOOD, I'M GLAD WE COULD HAVE
THIS LITTLE TALK STANLEY.
NOW YOU GO OUTSIDE AND
PRACTICE FOOTBALL
LIKE A GOOD
LITTLE HETEROSEXUAL.
( Cartman )
YOU GUYS SEE ME BLOCK
THAT DEFENSE TODAY?
I WAS KICKING ASS.
YOU'RE GONNA NEED TO
KICK MORE ASS THAN THAT
TO BEAT THE COWBOYS.
HEY, SPEAKING OF
POUNDING ASS,
HERE COMES STAN'S
LITTLE HOMO DOG!
SHUT UP DUDE!
SPARKY, WHERE'D YOU
GET THAT PINK SCARF?
WOOF, WOOF.
THAT IS THE GAYEST
DOG I HAVE EVER SEEN.
HE JUST NEEDS SOME
TRAINING, THAT'S ALL.
SIT SPARKY.
GOD BOY,
NOW SHAKE.
GOOD BOY, NOW,
DON'T BE GAY!
DON'T BE GAY
SPARK.
DON'T BE GAY.
DID IT WORK?
I DON'T KNOW.
HE STILL LOOKS
PRETTY GAY TO ME.
HEY STAN,
YOUR DOG BEEN TO ANY
ANY PRIDE MARCHES LATELY?
YEAH, MAYBE YOU
SHOULD TAKE HIM TO
A BARBRA STREISAND CONCERT!
STUPID GAY DOG.
COME ON YOU GUYS,
I HAVE AN IDEA.
I WANT $500 ON
THE SOUTH PARK COWS.
ARE YOU CRAZY?
NO SIREE,
I'M TELLING YOU,
I GOT THE LINE.
MY NEPHEW STAN IS
THE BEST QUARTERBACK
THE SCHOOL'S
EVER SEEN.
I GUARANTEE THEY'LL
BEAT THE SPREAD.
( man )
I'M GONNA PUT ALL
MY MONEY ON THE COWS.
I'LL PUT $300
ON THE COWS TOO...
( chatter )
WHOA, WHOA.
DON'T GET TOO
CARRIED AWAY NOW.
YOU BETTER BE RIGHT
ABOUT THIS JIMBO.
DON'T WORRY YOURSELF.
ARE YOU SURE STAN
IS THAT GOOD?
NOT THAT SURE.
I THINK WE BETTER COME UP
WITH A BACK-UP PLAN.
LET'S SEE HERE.
HEY BOOKIE,
WHAT'S THE HALF-TIME
SHOW GONNA BE?
YOU HAVEN'T HEARD?
JOHN STAMOS' OLDER
BROTHER RICHARD STAMOS
IS GONNA SING
"LOVING YOU".
I LOVE THAT SONG.
"LOVING YOU",
THAT'S PERFECT.
COME ON NED,
MIDDLE PARK IS GONNA
GET A HALF-TIME SHOW
THEY'LL NEVER FORGET.
NOW WHY DON'T...
DAMMIT SPARKY,
WHERE DO YOU KEEP
GETTING THIS THING?
NO PINK BANDANA
SPARKY, BAD DOG!
NOW PAY
ATTENTION--
SPARKY THIS IS
FIFI, OOH LA-LA!
THERE HE GOES.
THAT-A-BOY SPARK,
GET HER!
YES!
AH CRAP, NOW
WHAT DO I DO?
WHO CARES IF
YOUR DOG IS GAY.
MAYBE IT'S
NOT THAT BAD.
NO WAY DUDE,
MY MOM SAYS GOD
HATES GAY PEOPLE.
THAT'S WHY HE "SMOKED"
THE SODOMIES IN FRANCE.
( mumbling )
I KNOW, MR. GARRISON SAID
HOMOSEXUALS ARE EVIL.
BUT SPARKY DOESN'T
SEEM EVIL.
MAYBE MR. GARRISON
IS WRONG.
YOU SHOULD ASK
SOMEBODY ELSE.
LIKE WHO?
And now back to...
on South Park
Public Access.
Ye, many of you
are seeking answers,
and I am the way
for you, my children.
Let's open the
phone lines back up
for some questions.
Hello caller,
you're on the air.
Yeah, is
this Jesus?
Yes my son.
This is Robert
from Torre Pines,
I called last week asking
for advice on my ex-wife.
Of course Robert,
how are things now?
Everything is much
better Jesus,
she hasn't
mouthed-off since.
I just wanted to
thank you for
the advice.
Oh, and for dying
for my sins too,
that was really
nice of you.
Blessed art thou,
Robert.
Next caller,
you're on the air.
( Stan )
Hi Jesus, I have
a dog and he's a,
he's a homosexual.
My son,
a lot of people
have wondered
what my stance
on homosexuality is,
so I'd like to state
once and for all
my true opinion.
You see...
That's all the time
we have left
for "Jesus and Pals",
now stay tuned for
"Marty's Movie Reviews".
WHAT'D HE SAY?
I GOT CUT OFF FOR
"MARTY'S STUPID
MOVIE REVIEWS"!
"MARTY'S MOVIE REVIEWS"
ARE ON, KICK ASS!
ISN'T THERE ANYBODY
WHO CAN HELP ME?
WHO CARES?
COME ON DUDE,
WE HAVE TO GET
TO PRACTICE.
IT'S NOT OKAY, I DON'T
WANT A GAY DOG.
I WANT A BUTCH DOG,
I WANT A "RIN TIN TIN".
NOW CHILDREN,
WE'VE GOT TO HANDLE
THE BALL BETTER.
YOU'VE GOT TO
HOLD YOUR FOOTBALL
LIKE YOU WOULD
HOLD YOUR LOVER.
GENTLY, YET FIRMLY.
YOU WANT TO BE BOTH
NURTURING AND CLINGING
AT THE SAME TIME.
OH YEAH...
♪ JUST LIKE MAKING SWEET
LOVE TO THE FOOTBALL ♪
♪ BEING NAUGHTY
WITH THE FOOTBALL ♪
♪ MMM ♪
CHEF!
♪ EVER SO GENTLY ♪
CHEF?
CHEF!
OH, SORRY CHILDREN.
LET'S RUN
SOME PLAYS.
MR. CHEF SIR?
NO PIP, WE STILL DON'T
HAVE A HELMET FOR YOU.
RIGHTO, BUT HOW ABOUT,
I'LL USE A HELMET TODAY,
AND ONE OF THE OTHER
CHILDREN GOES WITHOUT.
THAT WOULDN'T BE FAIR
TO THE OTHER CHILDREN,
NOW WOULD IT?
I GUESS NOT.
WHAT WE WANT
TO DO HERE CARL,
IS PUT A TRIGGER ON THAT
BOMB THAT MAKES IT GO OFF
AT A SPECIFIC MOMENT
DURING HALF-TIME.
AND WHAT MOMENT
WOULD THAT BE?
WELL, JOHN STAMOS'
OLDER BROTHER
IS ALL SET TO SING
"LOVING YOU" DURING HALF-TIME.
WE WANT THAT BOMB TO GO OFF
WHEN HE HITS THAT HIGH "F".
WHAT HIGH F?
YOU KNOW,
♪ LOVING YOU ♪
♪ IS EASY 'CAUSE
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ DOOT-EN-DOOT-DOOT-DOO ♪
♪ AHH ♪
SO YOU WANT THE TRIGGER
ON THE "DOOT-EN-DOO"?
NO, DAMMIT,
THE "AAAH"!
AHH!
♪ DOOT-EN-DOOT-DOOT-DOO ♪
♪ AHH ♪
YOU GOT IT!
♪ DOOT-EN-DOOT-DOOT-DOO ♪
♪ AHH ♪
YEAH OKAY.
( chef )
WHAT'S THE
MATTER STAN?
YOU SEEM DOWN.
I CAN'T CONCENTRATE
BECAUSE MY DOG IS GAY.
WELL, YOU KNOW
WHAT THEY SAY--
YOU CAN'T TEACH A GAY DOG
STRAIGHT TRICKS.
OH STOP FILLING
HIS HEAD
WITH THAT QUEER-LOVING
PROPAGANDA!
SAY WHAT?
YOU OF ALL PEOPLE
SHOULD BE SYMPATHETIC.
WHAT DO
YOU MEAN?
WELL YOU'RE GAY,
AREN'T YOU?
WHAT THE HELL ARE
YOU TALKING ABOUT?!
I AM NOT GAY!
WELL, YOU SURE DO
ACT LIKE IT!
I JUST ACT THAT WAY
TO GET CHICKS, DUMB ASS.
WHAT'S THE
MATTER DUDE?
I DON'T KNOW
WHERE SPARKY IS.
HE USUALLY FOLLOWS ME
TO FOOTBALL PRACTICE.
MAYBE HE WENT SHOPPING
FOR SOME LEATHER PANTS.
OUCH!
HELLO THERE,
LITTLE PUP!
I'M BIG GAY AL.
HAVE YOU BEEN
OUTCAST?
WELL THEN I'M SO GLAD
YOU FOUND
MY BIG GAY
ANIMAL SANCTUARY.
WE'RE ALL BIG GAY
FRIENDS HERE.
WOULD YOU LIKE
TO LIVE WITH US?
COME ON IN
LITTLE FELLOW.
NOBODY WILL EVER
OPPRESS YOU HERE.
HAVE YOU GUYS
SEEN SPARKY?
HE STILL HASN'T
COME BACK.
WOW, IT'S BEEN
LIKE TWO DAYS.
I THINK HE MIGHT
HAVE RUN AWAY.
DID YOU CHECK
THE SHOPPING MALL...
OWW!
WE'LL LOOK FOR HIM
AFTER THE GAME STAN.
I'M NOT
PLAYING.
YOU'RE WHAT?
I'M NOT PLAYING
IN THAT STUPID GAME.
I HAVE TO
FIND MY DOG!
COME ON NED,
KEEP QUIET.
OKAY.
HELLO THERE ENRIQUE
WHAT ARE WE
DOING HERE?
WELL NED,
WE ALWAYS KIDNAP
MIDDLE PARK'S MASCOT.
BUT THIS YEAR WE'RE GONNA
BOOBY-TRAP IT INSTEAD
AND WHEN JOHN STAMOS'
OLDER BROTHER
HITS THAT HIGH "F"
IN "LOVING YOU",
BOOM!
NO MORE
MIDDLE PARK PLAYERS.
GODAMN, I LOVE
FOOTBALL!
SPARKY,
WHERE ARE YOU?
WHERE COULD HE BE?
( cheering )
HELLO EVERYONE,
THIS IS FRANK HAMMOND,
SOUTH PARK PUBLIC RADIO,
AM 900.
WELCOME TO
TONIGHT'S MATCH UP
BETWEEN THE
MIDDLE PARK COWBOYS
AND THE SOUTH PARK COWS.
WELL, IT LOOKS
LIKE CHEF,
THE SOUTH PARK COWS COACH,
IS A LITTLE NERVOUS.
THIS IS PROBABLY BECAUSE
HIS STAR QUARTERBACK
HAS YET TO SHOW UP.
OH, COME ON STAN.
MR. CHEF, IF STANLEY
DOESN'T SHOW UP,
CAN I USE
HIS HELMET?
NO PIP,
I'M SORRY!
SPARKY!
YOU'RE GONNA HAVE
TO QUARTERBACK KYLE.
BUT I NEVER PRACTICED
QUARTERBACK.
IT'S A LITTLE LATE
FOR THAT BULLCRAP NOW.
FILLING IN FOR
QUARTERBACK
IS NUMBER 12,
KYLE BROSLOVSKI.
HEY, HEY, WHERE'S
LITTLE STANLEY?
YEAH, WHY THE HELL IS
THAT LITTLE JEWISH KID
PLAYING
QUARTERBACK?!
NED LOOK.
THEY'VE GOT ENRIQUE
ON THEIR SIDELINES.
LOOKS LIKE THAT BOMB
IS STILL ATTACHED.
YEAH!
HI LITTLE FELLOW,
HOW ARE YOU
DOING TODAY?
FINE, HOW ARE YOU.
I'M SUPER,
THANKS FOR ASKING.
MY GAY DOG RAN AWAY
AND I WAS WONDERING IF
MAYBE HE CAME HERE.
WELL LET'S SEE,
COME ON IN.
DO YOU HAVE LOTS
OF GAY DOGS HERE?
WE HAVE ALL SORTS OF
GAY ANIMALS HERE
AT BIG GAY AL'S.
OVER HERE WE HAVE
A GAY LION.
ROAR!
AND WE HAVE
GAY WATER BUFFALO,
GAY HUMMING BIRDS,
HERE'S A GAGGLE
OF GAY GOOSES!
HI FELLOWS, IT'S
SO SUPER TO SEE YOU!
WOW, IT SEEMS LIKE
THE ANIMALS HERE
ARE REALLY HAPPY.
OF COURSE THEY ARE,
SILLY BUNS!
IT'S THE ONE PLACE
WHERE GAY ANIMALS
CAN REALLY
BE THEMSELVES.
DO YOU LIKE
TO DANCE?
( disco music )
( Kyle )
CARTMAN, YOU
HIKE ME THE BALL,
THEN SOMEBODY RUN
AND I'LL THROW IT
OR SOMETHING, READY?
BREAK!
YOU GUYS
ARE TOAST.
WE'RE GONNA POUND
YOUR HEADS IN.
WE'LL JUST
SEE ABOUT THAT!
( Kyle )
SET, SET...
( farting )
DAMN IT
CARTMAN!
WHAT'S
THE MATTER?
CARTMAN FARTED!
NO I DIDN'T, THAT
WAS JUST MY SHOES.
COME ON KYLE,
WE'LL GET A "DELAY
OF GAME" PENALTY!
NO WAY DUDE!
HIKE THE BALL!
DUDE WAIT...
THAT'S RIGHT,
YOU GOT BACK THERE.
THE BALL IS SNAPPED.
MIDDLE PARK BLITZES...
FUMBLE!
MIDDLE PARK
GETS THE BALL,
THEY RUN IT IN
FOR A TOUCHDOWN!
THE SCORE IS
7-0, MIDDLE PARK,
WITH 14:57 REMAINING
IN THE FIRST QUARTER.
HELLS BELLS!
I HAVEN'T SEEN
A BEATING LIKE THAT
SINCE RODNEY KING!
NOW FRANK, THAT'S
NOT VERY P.C.
YOU'RE GONNA GET US
IN TROUBLE AGAIN.
RIGHT, RIGHT,
I GOTTA WATCH THAT.
IF WE LOSE OUR MONEY
BECAUSE OF YOUR NEPHEW,
WE'RE GONNA HANG YOU
OUT TO DRY, JIMBO.
DON'T Y'ALL WORRY,
YOU JUST WAIT
'TIL HALF-TIME.
SPARKY!
HIYA SPARKY,
HOW'S IT GOING?
WOOF!
I MISSED YOU OLD PAL,
YOU REALLY HAD ME SCARED.
WOOF!
COME ON,
LET'S GO HOME.
I CAN STILL MAKE IT
IN TIME FOR THE GAME.
WE CAN WORK ON
MAKING YOU NOT GAY
TOGETHER.
SPARKY?
YOUNG MAN,
IT APPEARS YOU STILL
DON'T UNDERSTAND.
WHAT DON'T I
UNDERSTAND?
COME THIS WAY.
I HAVE TO SHOW
YOU SOMETHING.
JUST OVER A MINUTE TO GO
IN THE HALF.
THE SCORE IS
MIDDLE PARK COWBOYS 52,
SOUTH PARK COWS ZERO.
I HAVEN'T SEEN AN ENGLISHMAN
TAKE A BLOW LIKE THAT
SINCE HUGH GRANT!
DUDE, NOW THAT
IS NOT COOL.
SORRY, SORRY.
OKAY STAN, YOU
SHOULD GET IN LINE
FOR MY MY BIG
GAY BOAT RIDE.
STEP ABOARD
STANLEY.
HELLO EVERYONE,
AND WELCOME ABOARD
THE BIG GAY BOAT RIDE!
ON THIS ADVENTURE,
WE'LL BE SEEING
THE WORLD OF GAYNESS
THROUGHOUT TIME.
AND THE SOUTH PARK COWS
ARE SET TO RECEIVE,
THERE'S THE KICK.
IT'S TAKEN BY NUMBER 23,
KENNY McCORMICK.
HE'S AT THE 50,
THE 40, THE 30...
THE LITTLE RUNNING BACK
IS DOWN!
I THINK HE'S...
YES, HE'S BEEN
DECAPITATED!
OH MY GOD,
THEY KILLED KENNY!
YOU BASTARDS!
THAT'S GOTTA
HURT FRANK!
OUCHEROO!
HEY, COME ON,
THAT WAS "ROUGHING"!!
AT LEAST LET US
SCRAPE HIM OFF THE FIELD!
LOOKS LIKE THE
SOUTH PARK COWS
AREN'T EVEN GONNA BEAT
THE 72 POINT SPREAD,
NOT BY A LONG SHOT.
YOU SEE,
GAYNESS HAS EXISTED SINCE
THE BEGINNING OF TIME.
FROM THE EGYPTIAN PHARAOHS,
TO THE SHOGUNS
OF JAPAN.
UH-OH, LOOK OUT,
IT'S THE OPPRESSORS!
CHRISTIANS AND REPUBLICANS
AND NAZIS, OH MY!
( gunshot )
OH, GOSH,
THAT WAS CLOSE.
OKAY, LET'S STEER
OUR BIG GAY BOAT
OUT OF HERE,
AND INTO A PLACE WHERE GAYS
ARE ALLOWED TO LIVE FREELY.
♪ WE ARE GAY,
AND IT'S OKAY ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GAY MEANS HAPPY
AND HAPPY MEANS GAY ♪
♪ WE'RE NOT SAD
ANYMORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE WE'RE OUT
THE CLOSET DOOR ♪
♪ IT'S OKAY, HEY,
TO BE GAY ♪♪
SO, WHAT DO YOU
THINK STAN?
THIS KICKS ASS.
I'M SORRY I TRIED
TO CHANGE YOU, SPARK.
I JUST DIDN'T
UNDERSTAND.
ISN'T THIS PRECIOUS?
AND NOW HERE TO SING
THE TOUCHING SONG
"LOVING YOU",
IS THE ONE AND ONLY,
JOHN STAMOS' BROTHER!
ALRIGHT RICHARD!
♪ LOVING YOU ♪
♪ IS EASY
'CAUSE YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ DOOT-EN-DOOT-DOOT-DOO ♪
♪ AH... AH... ♪
WHAT THE HELL?
HE DIDN'T SING
THE HIGH "F"!
RICHARD STAMOS CAN'T
SING A HIGH "F",
HE ALWAYS SCREWS
IT UP LIKE THIS.
NED, WE ARE GONNA
GET OUR ASSES KICKED!
♪ LA, LA, LA,
LA, LA ♪
IT'S OBVIOUS WHERE
ALL THE TALENT
IN THAT FAMILY WENT!
THANKS FOR
EVERYTHING
BIG GAY AL.
WOOF!
NO PROBLEM KIDS.
ARE YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT TO STAY FOR
SOME TOASTED
CHEESE SANDWICHES?
NO THANKS,
I GOTTA GET BACK FOR
THE BIG FOOTBALL GAME.
COME ON BOY.
OH STAN...
WHEN YOU GET
BACK TO TOWN,
TELL THEM ABOUT US
WILL YOU?
TELL THEM THERE ARE
GAY ANIMALS HERE,
WHO NEED HOMES,
DESPERATELY.
I WILL BIG GAY AL,
I WILL.
OH, MY CARROT CAKE.
THESE SOUTH PARK COWS
ARE BEING ABSOLUTELY
MOLESTED BY MIDDLE PARK.
I HAVEN'T SEEN SO MANY
CHILDREN MOLESTED SINCE...
I THOUGHT YOU SAID
BEATING THE SPREAD
WAS A SURE THING,
JIMBO!
( Mr. Hat )
YEAH, WE ALL PUT OUR
LIFE SAVING IN THIS GAME!
YOU'RE A DEAD
MAN JIMBO!
THIS SHOULD JUST ABOUT
WRAP IT UP...
WAIT A MINUTE,
WHAT'S THIS?
YEAH, YAHOO!
IT'S STAN, THE SOUTH PARK
STAR QUARTERBACK.
WHERE THE HELL
HAVE YOU BEEN STAN?
I'VE BEEN GETTING
MY BEST FRIEND BACK.
JUST GET
IN THERE BOY.
GIVE THEM HELL
STANLEY!
JESUS, NOW I HAVEN'T
ASKED YOU FOR MUCH.
ALL WE NEED IS
ONE LITTLE SCORE.
PLEASE,
PLEASE JESUS.
LEAVE ME ALONE!
STAN HIKES THE BALL,
HE STEPS BACK
TO PASS.
HEY STAN,
I'M OPEN I THINK.
AND HE THROWS IT TO KYLE,
THE LITTLE JEWISH KID.
OH MY!
I HAVEN'T SEEN A JEW
RUN LIKE THAT
SINCE POLAND, 1938!
DUDE!
TOUCHDOWN.
YEAH.
THE CLOCK RUNS OUT
AND THE FINAL SCORE IS
MIDDLE PARK COWBOYS 73,
SOUTH PARK COWS 6.
SOUTH PARK
BEATS THE SPREAD.
YEAH!
SPEECH.
STAN, WHAT DO YOU WANT
TO TELL THE WORLD
ABOUT THIS STUNNING,
ALMOST VICTORY?
IT'S REALLY COOL
THAT WE BEAT THE SPREAD
AGAINST THE COWBOYS.
YEAH, RIGHT!
AND MAYBE WE CAN BEAT 'EM
EVEN MORE NEXT YEAR.
AND IT'S OKAY
TO BE GAY.
( silence )
WHAT?
BEING GAY IS JUST
PART OF NATURE,
AND A BEAUTIFUL THING.
WHAT THE HELL IS
HE TALKING ABOUT?
STANLEY YOU ARRIVED
VERY LATE IN THE GAME.
WHERE WERE YOU
THAT WHOLE TIME?
I WAS WITH MY NEW
FRIEND, BIG GAY AL.
HE SHOWED ME HIS BIG GAY
ANIMAL SANCTUARY
AND TOOK ME ON
A BIG GAY BOAT RIDE,
WHERE I LEARNED ALL ABOUT
THE WONDERS OF GAIETY.
IT'S TRUE,
I'LL SHOW YOU.
BUT IT WAS HERE,
IT WAS ALL RIGHT HERE.
THERE WAS A TECHNO
DANCE CLUB.
YOU NEED TO LAY OFF
THE COUGH SYRUP.
ALRIGHT?
SERIOUSLY.
I'M WORRIED
ABOUT YOU MAN.
OLIVER!
I THOUGHT YOU
RAN AWAY
ALL THOSE MONTHS AGO.
SIDNEY!
WILLIE!
CARLOS!
I WANT TO
THANK YOU SO MUCH
FOR BRINGING
EVERYBODY HERE.
OH, THERE
YOU ARE DUDE.
HOW'S IT GOING?
I'M SUPER,
THANKS FOR ASKING.
IT LOOKS LIKE NOW
MY WORK HERE IS DONE.
GOODBYE STANLEY,
PEACE BE WITH YOU.
WOW!
YOU GUYS, YOU GUYS,
I CAN DO IT.
DO WHAT?
♪ LOVING YOU ♪
♪ IS EASY 'CAUSE
YOU'RE BEAUTIFUL ♪
♪ DOOT-EN-DOOT-DOOT-DOO ♪
♪ AHH ♪